Guide to the The Columbia Forum [Editorial Files]
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Journal Items
  - Comments
    - 1958-1960 (Box 70)
    - 1959-1962 (Box 71)
    - 1962-1966 (Box 72)
    - General (Box 72)
  - Letters
    - 1965-1966 (Box 72)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 73)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 74)
    - "Puff" letters, 1959-1970 (Box 74)
  - Comments from several groups, 1959-1970 (Box 74)
  - News Office — FORUM (Box 74)
  - Biographical "Blurbs" on Contributors (Box 75)
    - Biographical Notes, 1960-1962, 1965-1966 (Box 75)
    - Biographical Sketches, 1963-1966 (Box 75)
    - Bio Forms, 1964-1965 (Box 75)
    - Blurb Forms, 1966-1967 (Box 75)
    - Blurbs, 1967-1970 (Box 75)
  - Anthology (Box 76)
    - Advertising (Box 76)
    - Blurbs (Box 76)
    - Contract and Correspondence with Atheneum (Box 76)
    - Index (Box 76)
    - Introduction (Box 76)
    - Mailing, Questions and Problems (Box 76)
    - Permissions (Box 76)
    - Promotion (Box 76)
  - Summer Advertisement (Box 76)
  - Author Index (Box 77)
    - Name and address file (Box 77)
  - One oversize package
    - Computer printout- Columbia Forum Mailing List (Box Oversize 78)